It's so good! Yeah! You did that!
Hmm...
Pass it over here!
I got it! I got it!
Yeah!
Alright, yeah! No!
Ready? Ready?
What was that?
Give someone else a shot, too!
Wow look unbelievable in the
middle of the day too, huh?
She's doing it out here too.
Hey chimney girl, we're
in the middle of a game!
Raise your hands if you
want to get spanked. Huh?
Your turn, chimney girl! Nyah!
G-Get the ball!
Man, that's distracting.
You okay, Ashtray?
I can't move my lips.
You only played for two minutes.
This is what it's like when you get old.
No, that's the nicotine.
Does she need an ambulance?
I'm not done yet.
I'll be fine if I smoke a cigarette.
Excuse me, ma 'am.
Yeah, we received an anonymous report
of a suspicious person chasing children.
You really have to try to
be more careful, ma 'am.
Lucky for you, this
happened in Yagami Hara.
I'll be right back.
3401.
3401. 3401.
0101. Yeah!
Oh
That stinks!
What the hell is this?
God, that reeks.
It's like someone mopped
up coffee, cigarette,
and sandal soup with a rag
and left it in the sun!
Or like the concentrated stench
of human malice and bitterness.
Yeah, that's what it is.
It's Jaku-sa-bu-bura!
The demon Astaroth is
upon us, chain-smoker!
We need to evacuate as soon as possible!
Do you even understand how bad this is?
There are over 70 carcinogens
in cigarettes. Seventy!
Not to mention that
secondhand smoke is a serious
nuisance to non-smoking
neighbors like myself.
Am I getting through to you, Chainsmoker?
Your chance of having
a stroke has doubled.
Cigarette smoke deteriorates
your blood vessels.
There is proof that it
causes heart failure.
Naggy, naggy, naggy.
Anyway, here's my point.
A friend of mine is holding a
smoking addiction seminar nearby?
so I brought you this pamphlet.
Right over here.
Damn, can't see too well.
Where'd I leave it?
Man, this place is gross.
Is that it?
I don't know, I guess not.
Oh, you got a face on
the back of your head!
Looks like you're a nicotine
addict too, Landlord!
Sorry hold off on the jokes
until my face heals a bit.
Wait, what's wrong?
What the hell did you put
on me you fucking cat?
Huh?
I don't feel good.
Or is this just a sense of guilt?
Sure, she's got shit manners, and
that's her fault a hundred percent,
but maybe I'm being too harsh towards her.
Dammit, not again.
Using a sense of righteousness as
an excuse to make myself feel good.
I'm sorry, Aniko.
Maybe I was too rude just about it.
What the hell are you doing?
This is the life.
Chain Smoker Cat!
Yeah...
Yeah... Oh, oh!
Ah!
Ch-ch-ch...
Right...
Hold on, how many fucking
cigarettes are you going to smoke?
Do you understand what a mess you're in?
Sir, yes, sir.
You said if I gave you an extension,
you'd do anything to repay me, and
that anything is weeding the lot.
Sir, yes, sir.
And here you are in a cigarette
break five minutes into the job,
and you need a second one already?
Seriously?
Sir, yes, sir.
And can we stop with the yes, please?
I'm confiscating this.
No, that's stealing!
Then I will evict you
for failing to pay rent
and littering cigarette
butts all over the lot,
dumbass!
You'll get it back when you're done!
No.
Oh.
Guess I could bring her some iced
tea or snacks when she's done.
Hey, are you eating something?
Horsetail Weeds, I got kinda hungry.
Oh, did you want some too, Mr. Landlord?
Of course not.
Just don't eat too many or
you'll get a stomach ache.
Yaniko, are you done yet?
I brought some snacks, so...
Huh?
No.
A cigarette?
And did she just grow a belly? Huh?
What happened to my cabbages?
Yeah.
Oh, wow, are those snacks for me?
Thanks!
But I'm pretty stuffed right now,
so I'll just save them for later.
Yummy.
Not my eyes!
Chainsmoker Cat!
That goddamn chimney.
She's always up to no good. Damn it!
Just thinking about her
gets me all riled up!
Riled up?
Riled... up...
Damage to wallpaper can become a significant
financial burden when you move out,
right?
Particularly when renting,
one should always be careful about any
discoloration of the walls from smoke.
The walls were painted this color
when I moved in and I ventilated
the room from time to time So I'm
sure it hasn't changed from smoking.
So I should be fine, right?
Wait, wasn't that poster?
Yeah, it was already up when I moved in
You think my property is haunted?
You can't be serious.
You're seeing stuff to me.
You liar!
There's talismans hidden on my wall,
and I heard some loud bangs
right after I found them.
That's not haunted, then what is landlord?
Just shut up!
There's no way to know what happened here!
Th-that's even more suspicious.
Oh, close call.
Hold me tighter!
I've been such a good girl!
Say, Yaniko.
What's up, Kansai?
I thought you said you told your baby
sister that you were swearing off the baka.
Isn't that right?
Your mouth disagrees
I'll quit for real this time.
This is the very last one.
I'll smoke.
That's so I admire the gumption
Oh
Little yon-yon acting the funny
man is as scarce as hands tea.
I gotta follow her up right with a
good punchline Coat your horses, girl.
You can't leave to buy milk already.
You gotta try and make it to kindergarten.
Wait a sec.
You didn't have a daddy growing up?
No, I did.
You're as cool as a jug
of branch water, Yan-Yan.
But I can't call myself a cat
from the West if I give up now.
If I can't get a laugh, then...
Oh, you nasty girl!
How'd this nose hook get here?
It was stuck in this issue of
manga I borrowed from the landlord.
I can't believe he put something
like this in a copy of Kirara.
How do you even use it?
You slip this bit on your
nose, and you go, boo.
You should try it on, then. You're nasty.
Yuck, that nose hook is
the tool of the devil.
Besides, it's not like we're
second cousins or something.
But I'm really curious.
You're curious about what?
Just leave me out of this. Icky.
You can't ask a young debutante like
myself to do such a thing, you chimney.
Well, now, wait a minute, though.
What if this is how I
can get her to crack up?
Well, dang it, just get it here.
Not gonna make this a habit.
Just split your sides already!
All right, I get it, you damn chimney.
You're meowing up the
wrong tree, little girl?
But you're gonna learn today
those your normal cigarettes!
Yeah, I treated myself and
bought some pricey ones.
But you don't get it. Oh,
I don't need any besides I was gonna
say about that bird on there Not sure
why they call them peace when the bird
looks like one of them migratory ones,
you know kind of like geese?
One can actually track
the ratio of beast folk to
humans by how many cigarettes
are sold in each region!
You can also tell if
citizens had to take out
any credit loans on
cars they'll never own.
Kinda like getting a car on lease.
Hey there, boss.
Can I take a break soon?
I've been working all day out here.
I got bills to pay, so I've been
busting my ass working as hard as I can.
Putting in elbow grease.
The suspect is currently fleeing
towards Kariba in a chop shop vehicle.
Mike, wait.
A vehicle carrying two greasy
pigs is coming through.
No, wait.
You can't call us pigs.
We're the police.
Wait, that's Beth Palmer's niece!
Then will an old face with double-P
signs finally make you laugh?
Humorous time!
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry with cherries on top, all right?
Jane Smoker Cat!
Mind if I come in?
Look who it is.
What's up, you honors?
I don't mind, but do you
like me or something?
Yeah.
Well, you don't ever complain when I
smoke and you let me drink for free,
so I guess I like that.
Well, okay.
I'm cool with whatever, though.
You cool with making me a drink, then?
Aw, man.
But that's such a pain.
Brought some smoked cheese bites for us.
I guess I can't really
say no to smoked cheese.
Appreciate it.
You can dump about half
a cup of whatever whiskey
you've got laying around
the house into a mug.
Follow it up with all
the syrup as you want.
And if you squirt, squirt, squirt some
lemon juice, then add some tap water.
You like it?
Impossible!
You got high standards, girl.
But I'm not gonna waste
any, so I'll finish it.
You care about the environment, huh?
The world's getting a little blurry.
Oh, wow.
The taste of all this blues is just...
the cherry on top.
It's nothing more than the first
step on the path to euphoria.
I think I need to lay down for a second.
I should probably call it quits too.
I'm still wrapped up in the
warm veil of boozy happiness
Oh, my God.
Aruko, you're down for a nightcap, right?
That drinking party was about
as much fun as a root canal.
Everyone was all smiles until I cracked a
joke and they said I was
desperate for laughs.
Sorry for trying to liven
up the party a little.
Smiling like a jackass
eating wires when they
don't got the guts to
crack a joke of their own.
No Sora, that cat won't hunt.
I was about to see St.
Peter myself, I stayed. Oh.
You're trying to beat
me to death's door, huh?
You little class clown.
James Boker Cat!
People of Nyagamihara
City, good afternoon.
This is a public service announcement.
We'd like to inform you that
the air is very dry today.
Please be careful when
you hit fire outdoors.
Make sure to put out any cigarettes
before throwing them away.
Wowza.
I never knew you had such
a beautiful voice, Kansai.
Kinda sounds like you're
faking it, though.
Sorry for making y 'all
help me out like this.
Seems like the person who
was supposed to help out
heard they're back at work
while eating a bento box.
Bento socks?
But they're made of cotton.
Man, what an idiot. Ha-ha.
Come on, now.
You can't shoot if we don't
got room to scoot, Yanniko.
Yakuko, open your window. G-got it.
Wouldn't it be funny as all get out
if we blasted a toot through the mic?
Yanniko, point it my way.
Get that tail higher.
That's a good girl.
You ready to blast out another one?
We're gonna let it ring loud
enough to wake the dead.
That'll get him laughing.
Okay, but that well's just
about run dry, Kansai.
I'll buy you smoke if you pass a good one.
You're on!
Sweet Jesus, you did it.
And it was a loud one too.
Can't they hear us talking too, though?
Keep those loud ones coming.
And you're on your way to free cigarettes.
Okay, I don't think maybe that's enough.
You have more of my size of this.
Who was that one?
Did you get shot in the van?
What the fuck is that one?
What on earth?
I got stuck.
Totally wouldn't be mad if
you gave me a push, Kansai.
How in the blue blazes
does this even happen?
My word is that soft.
I can't get any good grip.
You gotta flex them glutes.
I don't feel like I'm making
any progress at all, though.
I get it, but don't this sort of thing
look like we're batting for the other team?
It's okay.
Just try and bring me some
six from time to time.
You can't just give up.
I'm gonna give you a smack!
All you're doing is flexing your butt!
What are they scaring at?
What the same hell is wrong with them!
I'm not too much...
Why are we human beings?
No matter what else...
Why do you have to work?
Why don't you like it?
Why are you...
Hey!
Thank you.